flashracingonline.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy of racinghits.com web site.

Racinghits.com is firmly committed to the privacy of our users' personal information. Our staff, contractors and others who help us operate our web sites follow this policy on privacy and fair information practices for online activities of racinghits.com. We outline here the information-collection procedure and usage practices for our website, [www.racinghits.com](http://www.racinghits.com/). By using this website, you agree to accept this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below.

Your Information

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web page. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web page.

Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.

Links

Racinghits.com also links to a wide variety of other web sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

Questions or Suggestions

If you have any questions concerning the privacy policies of racinghits.com, please visit our Contact page.
